I can't get a comment
about how I should do
And I meet that pretty much I can say
So there I think there may be such a cultural difference
what might actually be meant as a joke
or as just small talk
gets in my world
something that closes the door
and I don't get the desire to continue that call
null
and it's just one example
say their opinion and what was interesting was to
I looked at Josefin that she thought it
was great fun, she really liked
with the
she was like, one says
in its proper element
in its proper element, that means that
that situation suited her
perfect
I, on the other hand, in one such
In such a call
In such a conversation culture where one speaks loudly